MUCHAMMAD ALIEF KURNIA WIJAYA

08138586506 | aliefkw26@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/aliefkurnia | github.com/alipk26

Cengkareng, Jakarta Barat

I am M Alief Kurnia W, 22 years old, a graduate of the PLN Institute of Technology in the Informatics Engineering study program as an Engineering graduate. With a great interest in the scope of Informatics Engineering as well as in the scope of Graphic Design, I believe I can help the company achieve its goals because I am quick to learn new things and can work individually or in a team.

Work Experiences

PT.Bifarma Adiluhung (KALBE) - Jakarta Timur

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

Graphic Designer

PT. Bifarma Adiluhung is a subsidiary of Kalbe which is engaged in genomics and I am in sales and marketing with the graphic design division and my jobdesk is:

- Poster, banner, flyer design for social media
- · Edit video for product branding
- · Responsible for making the genme.id website in terms of design and UI/UX

Digital Talent Scholarship

Student of Fresh Graduate Academy - Machine Learning Developer

The Fresh Graduate Academy Digital Talent Scholarship (FGA DTS) program is a training program to increase competence in the ICT field which aims to prepare graduates who have not or are not currently working to have professional competence, in accordance with the development of science and technology in the era of the industrial revolution 4.0 in

order to compete. in both domestic and foreign industries.

and what i got is

- · Programming With Python
- Image Classification with CNN
- · Create NLP models with tensorflow
- · Creating Machine Learning Models with Time Series Data

Education

Insitut Teknologi PLN - Jakarta, Indonesia

Nov 2018 - Nov 2022

Bachelor Degree in Computer Engineering with predicate Cum Laude, 3.66/4.00

Organisational Experience

Blue Thunder Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

Staff Media

• As a propaganda media staff in every content creation that will be uploaded on social media

BEM KBM STT-PLN Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

Dirjen Kreatif

- · Designing and designing every form of content that will be uploaded on social media
- · Designing an Entrepreneurship Seminar

Skills

- Programming Language: C++, Phyton, Javascript, C#
- Back End: NodeJs, MySQL, REST API, Postman, AWS
- Soft Skills: Creative, Good communication, Teamwork, Critical thinking, can learn new things quickly
- Hard Skills: Data Analyst, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Figma